https://www.ncjwc.org/privacy-policy/

National Council of Jewish Women of Canada
National Edmonton Simcoe County Toronto Vancouver Winnipeg ICJW
Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy Policy
PRIVACT POLICY STATEMENT
National Council of Jewish Women of Canada (NCJWC) recognizes the importance of and is committed to maintaining the accuracy, confidentially and security of your personal information.
NCJWC only collects personally identifying information from donors, clients, volunteers and event participants for fund raising, public education, and advocacy purposes, program and service delivery, as well as to establish, maintain and manage our relationship with you.
NCJWC is subject to the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). This means that should you correspond voluntarily with NCJWC by electronic mail or any other medium, the personal information that we hold, create and collect from you is used only for administrative and statistical purposes and is not shared or disclosed to anyone outside NCJWC without your permission.
NCJWC shares your mailing information only with employees and/or volunteers who require such information and who commit to keeping it confidential. We disclose your mailing information to the service provider whom we engage to mail our fundraising material.
When you send us e-mail, we will use your name and e-mail address only to respond to your requests or concerns or to provide you with information. Your e-mail may be shared with appropriate people within NCJWC to help us respond to your e-mail.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, or would like to access you personal information, please contact the National office.
National Council of Jewish Women of Canada 4700 Bathurst Street, Toronto, Ontario M2R 1W8 info@ncjwc.org
BE SOCIAL, CONNECT WITH US
© 2017 National Council of Jewish Women of Canada | Y5 Creative
Privacy Policy
Donations
Contact
